<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="/~d/styles/rss2full.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" media="screen" href="http://feeds.ign.com/~d/styles/itemcontent.css"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>IGN Video Games</title>
    <link>http://www.ign.com/articles</link>
    <description>The latest IGN news, reviews and videos about video games</description>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://feeds.ign.com/ign/games-all"/><feedburner:info xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" uri="ign/games-all"/><atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="hub" href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/"/><feedburner:feedFlare xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" href="https://add.my.yahoo.com/rss?url=http%3A%2F%2Ffeeds.ign.com%2Fign%2Fgames-all" src="http://us.i1.yimg.com/us.yimg.com/i/us/my/addtomyyahoo4.gif">Subscribe with My Yahoo!</feedburner:feedFlare><feedburner:feedFlare xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" href="http://fusion.google.com/add?feedurl=http%3A%2F%2Ffeeds.ign.com%2Fign%2Fgames-all" src="http://buttons.googlesyndication.com/fusion/add.gif">Subscribe with Google</feedburner:feedFlare><item>
      <title>Smash Bros. Ultimate: How to Unlock Every Character (Fastest Method)</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/08/smash-bros-ultimate-how-to-unlock-every-character-fastest-method</link>
      <description>Ready your fighter roster in Super Smash Bros. Ultimate with our guide to unlocking every character as quickly as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09358fe4b0c3a735a31376</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Unlock King K. Rool in Smash Bros. Ultimate</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/how-to-unlock-king-k-rool-in-smash-bros-ultimate</link>
      <description>Find out every way you can unlock the terrible lizard King K. Rool in Super Smash Bros. Ultimate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0b1ea1e4b0c3a735a31626</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Dead Online's Economy Update By the Numbers</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/red-dead-onlines-economy-update-by-the-numbers</link>
      <description>Does Red Dead Online's first update really do all that much to fix what so much of the early user base was complaining about?</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2018 00:10:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ae449e4b0b6ea190c96f3</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday, Red Dead Online got its <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/red-dead-online-first-update-promises-re-balanced-economy-and-player-gifts">first major update</a> after being in beta for more than a week. In a <a href="https://www.rockstargames.com/newswire/article/60735/Red-Dead-Online-Beta-Week-1-Update">post on their newswire</a>, Rockstar said the changes were  "specifically geared towards creating a more balanced, fun and rewarding overall experience, across all modes and missions," so of course, the big question is: does the update really do all that much to fix what so much of RDO's early user base was complaining about? The short answer is yes, it makes a huge difference - even if it doesn't fix all of the beta's problems.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/red-dead-onlines-economy-update-by-the-numbers">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jon Ryan</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-08T00:10:23Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smash Ultimate: How to Get Free, Powerful Spirits with Amiibo</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/smash-ultimate-how-to-get-free-powerful-spirits-with-amiibo</link>
      <description>Check out which non-fighter amiibo you can use to unlock powerful Spirits in Super Smash Bros. Ultimate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0aeba3e4b0b6ea190c9708</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joker in Smash Is ‘Emblematic’ of DLC Character Approach</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/nintendo-persona-5s-joker-is-emblematic-of-smash-bros-ultimates-dlc-approach</link>
      <description>Nintendo of America COO Reggie Fils-Aime says Joker should prime fans for the type of characters to expect from upcoming DLC.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 22:24:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ae9eae4b0c3a735a315c3</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the heels of last night’s announcement that <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/persona-5s-joker-is-coming-to-super-smash-bros-ultimate-as-dlc" target="_blank">Persona 5 protagonist Joker will join the Smash Bros. Ultimate roster</a>, Nintendo of America COO Reggie Fils-Aime says this reveal should prime fans for the type of characters to expect from the rest of the DLC.
</p><p>“It's emblematic of the approach that Mr. Sakurai and the team are taking with the DLC,” Fils-Aime told IGN. “He wants characters that are unique, different, to bring them into the Smash Bros. environment. So it's going to be tremendously exciting.”
</p><p>Fils-Aime explained that Sakurai and the team working on Ultimate’s DLC don’t necessarily see characters from franchises not typically associated with Nintendo as a limiting factor when it comes to Smash Bros.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/nintendo-persona-5s-joker-is-emblematic-of-smash-bros-ultimates-dlc-approach">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Andrew Goldfarb</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T22:24:51Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smash Bros: Controls and Basic Tips</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/smash-controls-and-basic-tips</link>
      <description>Starting Smash Bros. for the first time? See our explainer on controls and basic tips.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ae292e4b0b6ea190c96ec</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Awards 2018: The Best Moments From the Show</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/the-best-moments-from-the-game-awards-2018</link>
      <description>Here are our favorite moments from the Game Awards 2018.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ac08ae4b0775fa30cd06e</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Awards shows are a funny thing, but they're even funnier when they're paired with big video game announcements. You've got all the emotion and sincerity and awkwardness of a celebration show, paired with E3-style hype. Last night's Game Awards were a giddy mixture of the two, and there were some truly wonderful moments and surprises peppered throughout the near-3-hour show. Here are our highlights.
</p><p><em>Lucy O'Brien is Executive Editor of Features at IGN. Follow her on <a href="https://twitter.com/Luceobrien">Twitter.</a></em></p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/the-best-moments-from-the-game-awards-2018">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Lucy O'Brien</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T20:43:53Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioWare Further Details Anthem Demo Release Dates</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/bioware-announces-anthem-demo-release-date</link>
      <description>The Anthem developer revealed when you'll get your first shot piloting a Javelin and how to get in.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 20:17:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b8af239e4b01adbb49cc206</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em><strong>Update 12/7:</strong> </em>BioWare has given an update to when the demo for Anthem will be released, giving more specific time frames for when fans can expect to play it.
</p><p>Announced on <a href="https://www.ea.com/games/anthem/news/anthem-vip-demo" target="_blank">EA’s website</a>, there will be two release dates for the demo: one for “VIP” players, and an open demo soon after. The VIP demo will run from January 25–27 and be available to those who pre-order Anthem or are an EA Access or Origin Access subscriber at the time of the demo. Those who participate will also get an exclusive VIP demo item.
</p><p>The open demo will run from February 1-3 on PS4, Xbox One and PC and will be open to all players.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/bioware-announces-anthem-demo-release-date">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Brandin Tyrrel</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T20:17:45Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jak and Daxter Games Getting Limited Physical PS4 Release</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/jak-and-daxter-games-getting-limited-physical-ps4-release</link>
      <description>Sony, Naughty Dog, and Limited Run Games are giving all four Naughty Dog PS2 games physical releases on PS4.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:26:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ac306e4b0775fa30cd072</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sony, Naughty Dog, and Limited Run Games are collaborating to release physical PlayStation 4 versions of the original four Jak and Daxter games from the PlayStation 2, according to a post on the <a href="https://blog.us.playstation.com/2018/12/07/jak-and-daxter-gets-physical-ps4-versions-collectors-edition-releases/" target="_blank">PlayStation Blog</a>.
</p><p>It appears that the PlayStation 4 physical releases will contain the PS2 Classic versions of the games, which are currently available for download on the PS4. Jak and Daxter: The Precursor Legacy, Jak 2 and Jak 3 all received PlayStation 3 remasters, but it doesn't appear at this time that the remasters will be part of the PlayStation 4 physical releases. The fourth game, Jak X: Combat Racing, was not remastered for the PS3.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/jak-and-daxter-games-getting-limited-physical-ps4-release">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Nick Santangelo</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T19:26:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite: Every New Chest Location on the Season 7 Map</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/fortnite-every-new-chest-location-on-the-season-7-map</link>
      <description>See the new snowy glacier map in glorious ultra-high resolution -- with chests!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ac742e4b0b6ea190c96ba</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There Are Still Deals to Be Found on Nintendo Switch</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/the-best-nintendo-switch-deals-and-bundles</link>
      <description>Looking to grab a Nintendo Switch? Black Friday's Mario Kart bundle was arguably the best Nintendo Switch deal ever, but there are still chances to save.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:08:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0abf3ee4b0c3a735a31567</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>If you buy something through this post, IGN may get a share of the sale. For more, read our <a href="https://www.ziffdavis.com/terms-of-use#endorsement">Terms of Use</a>.</em>
</p><p>The Nintendo Switch is one of the hottest items of the 2018 holiday season, and as such, there aren't many Nintendo Switch deals happening right now. At least, there's nothing approaching the excellence of the Black Friday Nintendo Switch Mario Kart bundle.
</p><p>We've scoured the internet to come up with the best deals on Nintendo Switch consoles and bundles, and if you're after a new Nintendo Switch, the good news is there are still chances to save.
</p><p>Here are the best deals and sales on new Nintendo Switch bundles and consoles.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/the-best-nintendo-switch-deals-and-bundles">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <media:content height="466" type="image/jpeg" width="720" url="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2028/09/Aces-720x466.jpg"/>
      <dc:creator>Seth G. Macy</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T19:08:30Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Dead Redemption 2, God of War Dominate at The Game Awards 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/the-game-awards-2018-all-the-winners</link>
      <description>God of War and Red Dead Redemption 2 the big winners on the night.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:07:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09e6cae4b0c3a735a31482</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celebrating everything from AAA blockbusters like Red Dead Redemption II to esports star SonicFox, here's the full list of finalists and winners from The Game Awards 2018.
</p><p><h2><strong>Game of the Year</strong></h2>
</p><p><ul>
</p><p>	<li>Assassin’s Creed Odyssey</li>
</p><p>	<li>Celeste</li>
</p><p>	<li><strong>God of War - WINNER</strong></li>
</p><p>	<li>Marvel’s Spider-Man</li>
</p><p>	<li>Monster Hunter: World</li>
</p><p>	<li>Red Dead Redemption II</li>
</p><p></ul>
</p><p><h2><strong>Best Action Game</strong></h2>
</p><p><ul>
</p><p>	<li>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4</li>
</p><p>	<li><strong>Dead Cells - WINNER</strong></li>
</p><p>	<li>Destiny 2: Forsaken</li>
</p><p>	<li>Far Cry 5</li>
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/the-game-awards-2018-all-the-winners">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Dan Crowd</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T19:07:16Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Is SonicFox, the esports Champion Who Stole the Show at The Game Awards?</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/who-is-the-game-awards-2018-best-esports-player-sonicfox</link>
      <description>Here's what you need to know about SonicFox, the esports champion who stole the show at The Game Awards.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 18:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0a0563e4b0c3a735a314b6</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>"I'm gay, black, a furry - pretty much everything a Republican hates - and the best esports player of the year, I guess."
</p><p>With an acceptance speech like that, it's no surprise that people might be wondering who Dominique "SonicFox" McLean is. The short answer is that the winner of Best Esports Player at the 2018 Game Awards is an absolute fighting game machine. The four-time EVO champion has destroyed his competition in games like Injustice: God's Among Us, Mortal Kombat X, and more recently Dragon Ball FighterZ. And he's done it all while sporting a set of blue ears.
</p><p>One of the most notable things about SonicFox, compared to other esports champions, is his ability to not only flex into other games but to dominate in them. He also has a tendency to play large character pools or even stick to those often considered weaker like his Joker choice for Injustice 2. At only 20 years old, he's one of the most successful players of all time, and is commonly believed to currently be the highest-paid fighting game esports champ around.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/who-is-the-game-awards-2018-best-esports-player-sonicfox">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Hope Corrigan</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T18:30:04Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devil May Cry 5: New Character Details Revealed</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/devil-may-cry-5-new-character-details-revealed</link>
      <description>Capcom has released an extended trailer for Devil May Cry 5, and has given more information on the new character V.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:38:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0aafd6e4b0775fa30cd049</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Devil May Cry 5 received a brief new trailer during The Game Awards last night, but Capcom has released an extended trailer and more information on the new character V.
</p><p>V is touted as a deceptively strong character that can summon three different demons to assist him in battle. Shadow is a fast, panther-like creature that can morph into blades and needles for close-range combat. Griffon is a bird-like demon that can carry V across large areas and fire beams of light to destroy incoming enemies. Nightmare is a massive demon that crushes enemies that get in his path, and can also utilize beams of light.
</p><p>Using all three demons to your advantage, V can enter battle after enemy health has been whittled down to make a final blow with his cane attack. V and his demons can be seen in action in the extended trailer below.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/devil-may-cry-5-new-character-details-revealed">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Colin Stevens</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T17:38:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Battle Edition Announced, Features Only Multiplayer and Blackout</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-battle-edition-announced-features-only-multiplayer-and-blackout</link>
      <description>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Battle Edition for PC gets players a Zombies-less experience on the cheap.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 17:09:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0a9023e4b0c3a735a31507</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 PC players can now get Black Ops 4 without Zombies.
</p><p><a href="https://investor.activision.com/news-releases/news-release-details/call-duty-black-ops-4-battle-edition-available-now-pc" target="_blank">Activision Blizzard has announced</a> Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 Battle Edition, available on <a href="https://us.shop.battle.net/en-us/product/call-of-duty-black-ops-4?p=46750" target="_blank">Battle.net</a>, that features just the multiplayer and Blackout modes for the limited time price of $30. Players have the option to upgrade to the Digital Standard Edition to get Zombies mode, 1,100 Call of Duty Points, and various bonus items for an undisclosed price.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/call-of-duty-black-ops-4-battle-edition-announced-features-only-multiplayer-and-blackout">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Shabana Arif</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T17:09:48Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smash Bros: See the Full Vs. Mode Character Unlock Order</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/smash-bros-see-the-full-vs-mode-character-unlock-order</link>
      <description>See the list of fighters you can unlock in Super Smash Bros. Ultimate by playing regular matches, and how you can speed things up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0a36e2e4b0c3a735a314c7</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Outer Worlds Is Bringing Fun Back to Science Fiction</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/the-outer-worlds-is-bringing-fun-back-to-science-fiction</link>
      <description>Obsidian's newly announced Sci-Fi RPG has a dark sense of humor slathering its corporate world.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 14:15:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0a3c70e4b0b6ea190c9625</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Obsidian is no stranger to good roleplaying games. For more than a decade the developer behind Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic 2, Fallout: New Vegas, the Pillars of Eternity series, and more has delivered the kind of strange and fantastical worlds where players can get lost saving the world, or dooming it. Now, the studio is back at it again with a new sci-fi slice of fresh hell to get lost in: The Outer Worlds.
</p><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/obsidian-announces-new-sci-fi-rpg-the-outer-worlds" target="_blank">The Outer Worlds is something new for Obsidian</a>. It’s not concerned with dragons and elves, or post-apocalyptic desert bugs and raiders. There are no Jedi (that I know of.)
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/the-outer-worlds-is-bringing-fun-back-to-science-fiction">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Brandin Tyrrel</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T14:15:48Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Money in Red Dead Online</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/how-to-make-money-in-red-dead-online</link>
      <description>Whether you need cash quick early on or want to figure out the most efficient loop, here's the best ways to earn money in Red Dead online.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c00c056e4b0775fa30cc99b</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Win a Nintendo Switch Super Smash Bros. Ultimate Bundle</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/win-a-nintendo-switch-super-smash-bros-ultimate-bundle</link>
      <description>We're giving away a Smash Bros. Ultimate Nintendo Switch bundle.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 12:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c07ed13e4b0b6ea190c93b7</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em><strong>This competition is sponsored by Nintendo.</strong></em>
</p><p>The game Nintendo fans have been waiting for is almost here, with Super Smash Bros. landing on Switch on 7 December. We have a Super Smash Bros. Ultimate Pack to give away to one lucky winner!
</p><p><p style="text-align: center"><img class=" wp-image-2064187 aligncenter" alt="11896606-1674631748905220" src="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2018/12/11896606-1674631748905220.jpg" width="360" height="360" /></p>
</p><p>This awesome bundle includes a limited edition dock decorated with  fighters from the  game, Super Smash Bros. design Joy-Con controllers and of course a copy of Super Smash Bros. Ultimate.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/win-a-nintendo-switch-super-smash-bros-ultimate-bundle">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <media:content height="360" type="image/jpeg" width="360" url="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2018/12/11896606-1674631748905220.jpg"/>
      <dc:creator>IGN Staff</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T12:00:55Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Defense Force 5 Review</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/earth-defense-force-5-review</link>
      <description>Even with dated graphics, EDF 5 is an energetic essay on action game design that is way too much fun to miss.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 11:00:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09b57ee4b0c3a735a3141f</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><p dir="ltr">In real life, I don’t like creepy crawly things. I’m terrified of spiders, appalled by roaches, scared stupid of wasps, and refuse to touch any animal that might be deemed “slimy.” My wife kills all the bugs in our house. That fear adds a little gravity and catharsis to fighting the thousands of house-sized monstrosities in EDF 5 – and “thousands” is no hyperbole. During my playthrough of Earth Defense Force 5, I have thus far killed precisely 21,369 space aliens, murderous robots, and giant insects. I know this because the record-keeping department of the Earth Defense Force tells me so, and yet somehow even that astronomical number seems far too low for the amount of satisfaction I’ve derived from it – even before jumping into the excellent co-op multiplayer.</p>
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/07/earth-defense-force-5-review">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jared Petty</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T11:00:22Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far Cry New Dawn: Making the Apocalypse Great Again</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/far-cry-new-dawn-making-the-apocalypse-great-again</link>
      <description>Far Cry New Dawn sets the series after a nuclear apocalypse and it's never look so inviting.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 07:30:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c08ff4be4b0b6ea190c94c4</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><p dir="ltr">Set 17 years after the climax of Far Cry 5 – which, if you’re not aware, saw Joseph Seed’s religious cult detonate a series of nuclear warheads around the Northern hemisphere – Far Cry New Dawn carves out another story of uprising and resistance amidst the fallout.</p>
</p><p><p dir="ltr">Yes, Far Cry’s latest entry is set in a post-apocalyptic world, but crucially, it’s one that’s trying to resist all the cliches that setting might suggest.</p>
</p><p><p dir="ltr"></p><p></p>
</p><p><p dir="ltr">A lot of what you might expect from the apocalypse has already passed. The US has endured a long and brutal nuclear winter, where nothing grew and almost everything died. Nearly two decades later, nature has enthusiastically reclaimed what humankind lost – New Dawn presents the most lush and inviting apocalypse imaginable.</p>
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/far-cry-new-dawn-making-the-apocalypse-great-again">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Daniel Krupa</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T07:30:01Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persona 5's Protagonist Is Coming to Super Smash Bros. Ultimate</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/persona-5s-joker-is-coming-to-super-smash-bros-ultimate-as-dlc</link>
      <description>Joker will join Super Smash Bros. Ultimate as its first Challenger Pack character.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:32:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09f7c7e4b0775fa30ccfa2</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Super Smash Bros. Ultimate's first DLC fighter features Persona 5's protagonist, Joker.
</p><p>"This gives you a flavor of how we're approaching the DLC," Reggie Fils-Aime said at The Game Awards. "There's going to be five characters. Each character will come with a stage </p><p> it'll come with a collection of music. These are characters that are new to the series... characters that you would not anticipate to be in Super Smash Bros. Ultimate."
</p><p>The first challenger pack was not given a release date on stage at The Game Awards.
</p><p><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/super-smash-bros-ultimate-review">IGN gave Super Smash Bros. Ultimate a 9.4</a> for its comprehensiveness and improvements. Learn <a href="https://www.ign.com/wikis/super-smash-bros-switch/How_to_Unlock_All_Characters_in_Smash_Bros._Ultimate">the fastest way to unlock every character</a> in Super Smash Bros. Ultimate with this guide.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/persona-5s-joker-is-coming-to-super-smash-bros-ultimate-as-dlc">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Miranda Sanchez</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T04:32:06Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite's The Block Will Feature Player Creations in Battle Royale</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/fortnites-the-block-will-feature-player-creations-in-battle-royale</link>
      <description>The Block is a new area in Fortnite Battle Royale and will feature user created buildings and creations.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:27:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09f6c2e4b0c3a735a314a0</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new area named The Block has been added to the Fortnite Battle Royale map and will feature user created structures and creations.
</p><p>Creative Director Donald Mustard shared the news on stage during today's Game Awards presentation. The Block will feature player maps made in Creative, the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/05/fortnite-creative-allows-you-to-create-your-own-private-island">brand new mode</a> where players can build and customize their own private island. Epic will ultimately pick which creations are featured.
</p><p>Not every private island will be eligible for The Block. User creations must fit neatly into a 25x25 tile area within the flat section of the island. Memory usage must be kept below 50,000 and chest, floor loot, and vehicle spawns will be added by Epic.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/fortnites-the-block-will-feature-player-creations-in-battle-royale">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <media:content height="405" type="image/png" width="720" url="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2018/12/s7extra3-720x405.png">
        <media:description type="html">id=</media:description>
      </media:content>
      <dc:creator>Michael Koczwara</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T04:27:45Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rage 2 Release Date Announced</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/rage-2-release-date-announced</link>
      <description>Bethesda has finally spilled the beans on Rage 2’s long-awaited launch date.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:22:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0873bde4b0c3a735a31317</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At The Game Awards tonight, Bethesda announced that Rage 2 will be released for Xbox One, PlayStation 4, and PC on May 14, 2019.
</p><p>The announcement came alongside a new trailer showing off new gameplay and our best look yet at some of the big new features.
</p><p>Rage 2 was <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/05/14/rage-2-officially-announced" target="_blank">first announced</a> earlier this year ahead of E3, and <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/05/15/rage-2-release-window-gameplay-details-announced" target="_blank">previously scheduled</a> for Spring 2019 without any specific release date.
</p><p>For much more on Rage 2, read about the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/06/12/rage-2-a-love-affair-between-two-of-the-worlds-coolest-developers" target="_blank">collaboration between Id Software and Avalanche Studios</a>, plus all about the <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/06/12/e3-2018-rage-2-is-full-of-ways-to-murder-goons-with-superpowers" target="_blank">many superpowers that will let you take down post-apocalyptic enemies</a> and <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/06/24/e3-2018-rage-2-looks-like-a-great-id-game-but-what-about-its-open-world" target="_blank">Rage 2’s wide open world</a>.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/rage-2-release-date-announced">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Andrew Goldfarb</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T04:22:43Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's Your First Bloody Look at Mortal Kombat 11</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/heres-your-first-bloody-look-at-mortal-kombat-11</link>
      <description>Mortal Kombat 11 has been officially announced by NetherRealm Studios at The Game Awards.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 04:05:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0863f8e4b0775fa30ccdd0</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mortal Kombat 11 has been officially announced by NetherRealm Studios at The Game Awards, with a release date of April 23, 2019.
</p><p>The trailer (teased by Ed Boon as an award for best sports/racing game), showed off a lot, including Scorpian vs Evil Raiden, weapons, classic Scorpion and best of all, lots and lots of gore. Check out the trailer below.
</p><p>Though this is the first time we've seen Mortal Kombat 11, murmurings of its existence began in November after Spanish-language voice actor José Eduardo Garza Escudero <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/11/20/voice-actor-claims-mortal-kombat-11-is-on-the-way">tweeted his disappointment</a> at being removed from the game by localization company Pink Noise Studios.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/heres-your-first-bloody-look-at-mortal-kombat-11">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Lucy O'Brien</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T04:05:53Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranger Things 3: The Game Revealed</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/stranger-things-3-the-game-announced</link>
      <description>This upcoming game will follow the events of Stranger Things' third season.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:57:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09efb7e4b0b6ea190c95fc</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A 16-bit Stranger Things Season 3 video game is in development by BonusXP,  Stranger Things series creators Matt and Ross Duffer announced at The Game Awards.
</p><p>This co-op beat 'em up is based on the third season of the popular Netflix show. According to a Tweet from Netflix, Stranger Things 3: The Game is coming "to all platforms." The trailer showed Chief Hopper, Lucas, and Steve fighting foes in various areas.
</p><p>The first Stranger Things game developed by BonusXP was released on mobile devices in October 2017.
</p><p><em>Miranda Sanchez is a senior editor at IGN. You can chat with her about video games and anime on <a href="https://twitter.com/HavokRose">Twitter</a>.</em></p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/stranger-things-3-the-game-announced">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Miranda Sanchez</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:57:43Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Game From Giant Squid Looks Stunning</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/the-pathless-announced-at-the-game-awards-2018</link>
      <description>Giant Squid, the developer behind Abzu, announced The Pathless at the Game Awards, 2018.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:55:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09ec66e4b0775fa30ccf84</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Giant Squid, the developer behind Abzu, announced The Pathless at the Game Awards, 2018.
</p><p>The Pathless looks to be a beautiful stylized platformer centered on a woman and a bird she rescues who helps her traverse its giant, beast-peppered landscape.  No other details were revealed, but you can check out the trailer and stills for The Pathless below.
</p><p><em>Lucy O'Brien is Games &amp; Entertainment Editor at IGN’s Sydney office. Follow her on <a href="https://twitter.com/Luceobrien" rel="nofollow">Twitter.</a></em></p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/the-pathless-announced-at-the-game-awards-2018">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Lucy O'Brien</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:55:23Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashen Available Now</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/ashen-available-now-journey-on-pc-for-the-first-time</link>
      <description>Ashen is now available on the Epic Games Store and Xbox One with Journey coming to the storefront soon for PC.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09eda6e4b0b6ea190c95ef</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ashen is now available on the Epic Games Store and Xbox One, with Journey coming to the Epic Games Store soon for PC.
</p><p>Ashen can be purchased for $40 USD on the <a href="https://news.xbox.com/en-us/2018/12/06/ashen-comes-to-xbox-one-and-xbox-game-pass/" target="_blank">Xbox One</a> (and is part of Xbox Game Pass) and for PC through the<a href="https://www.epicgames.com/store/en-US/product/ashen/home" target="_blank"> Epic Games Store</a>. Journey, which was previously exclusive to Sony consoles, is listed as <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/store/en-US/product/journey/home" target="_blank">coming soon.</a>
</p><p><blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
</p><p><p dir="ltr" lang="en">surprise <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AshenGame?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AshenGame</a> and Journey</p>
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/ashen-available-now-journey-on-pc-for-the-first-time">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Colin Stevens</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:51:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic The Gathering Esports Program Announced at The Game Awards 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/magic-the-gathering-esports-program-announced-at-the-game-awards-2018</link>
      <description>Hasbro and Wizards of the Coast announced a new esports program for Magic: The Gathering at The Game Awards 2018.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:48:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c05a862e4b0c3a735a310ae</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hasbro and Wizards of the Coast announced a new esports program for Magic: The Gathering at The Game Awards 2018.
</p><p>The program, which is coming in 2019, includes a $10 million prize bool across digital and tabletop Magic contests, with a $1 million Mythic Invitational at PAX East 2019. The Magic Pro League (MPL)  will establish a “new level of professional play” with 32 of the top ranked magic players worldwide. MPL players are offered play and streaming contracts worth $75,000, and members will play in weekly match-ups on Magic: The Gathering Arena.
</p><p>The Mythic Champion events are new flagship competitions for Magic: The Gathering Arena and tabletop Magic, which feature MPL players battling against challengers from the Magic community. More details on how players can enter and climb the ranks to battle these MPL players will be revealed in 2019.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/magic-the-gathering-esports-program-announced-at-the-game-awards-2018">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Colin Stevens</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:48:08Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUBG Gets Its First 6x6 Map, the Snowy Vikendi</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/pubg-gets-its-first-6x6-map-the-snowy-vikendi</link>
      <description>PUBG is getting its first 6x6 map, the snowy Vikendi, as well as a new assault rife and brand new Snowmobile.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:38:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09eacbe4b0c3a735a3148c</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PUBG is getting its first 6x6 map, the snowy Vikendi, as well as a new assault rife and brand new Snowmobile.
</p><p>Announced at The Game Awards, Vikendi is filled with snow, meaning players fighting for their chicken dinner will have to pay attention to their footprints as they trek through the wintry new map, as they can potentially lead others to their location.
</p><p>Vikendi will be available tonight on PC Test Server, and will launch on PC Live Server on December 19.
</p><p>Xbox One and PlayStation 4 owners will be able to try out the new map in January 2019.
</p><p>Tomorrow, December 7, <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/11/13/pubg-officially-announced-for-playstation-4" target="_blank">PUBG finally arrives on PlayStation 4,</a> making it almost a year since <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2017/10/31/playerunknowns-battlegrounds-releasing-on-xbox-game-preview-in-december" target="_blank">PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds joined Xbox Game Preview in December of 2017.</a>
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/pubg-gets-its-first-6x6-map-the-snowy-vikendi">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Adam Bankhurst</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:38:44Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlas: ARK: Survival Evolved Dev Announces New Game</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/atlas-ark-survival-evolved-dev-announces-new-game</link>
      <description>The open-world fantasy pirate MMO comes to PC next week, followed by an Xbox One release in 2019.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:38:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09eae6e4b0775fa30ccf7d</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Atlas, the next game from the developers of ARK: Survival Evolved, was announced tonight during The Game Awards.
</p><p>The open-world survival MMO will be released on PC via Steam on December 13, before coming to Xbox One in 2019 through Microsoft's Xbox Game Preview program.
</p><p>Atlas is developed by Grapeshot Games, a sister studio of ARK developer Studio Wildcard.
</p><p>Grapeshot Games describes Atlas as a "fantasy pirate adventure," promising shipbuilding, sailing, PvP battles, exploration, a vast skill tree, and a wide variety of creatures ranging from shoulder-mounted parrots to "gigantic sea monsters of legend." The developer also claims Atlas will support up to 40,000 players simultaneously.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/atlas-ark-survival-evolved-dev-announces-new-game">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jordan Sirani</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:38:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Man's Sky Dev Announces New Game, The Last Campfire</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/no-mans-sky-dev-announces-new-game-the-last-campfire</link>
      <description>Hello Games has announced The Last Campfire at The Game Awards 2018.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:14:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09a036e4b0c3a735a313e8</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hello Games, the developer behind No Man’s Sky and Joe Danger, has announced a smaller title called The Last Campfire at The Game Awards 2018.
</p><p>The Last Campfire is described as an adventure, telling the story of a lost Ember searching for meaning and a way home. It’s said to be filled with lost folk, strange creatures and mysterious ruins set in a beautiful wilderness. The trailer shows the player walking, rowing and climbing on their journey home.
</p><p>The developer is calling it a “Hello Games Short,” which, much like a Pixar short film, is designed to foster creativity and strengthen new voices within the studio on smaller titles. In this case, the creatives behind LostWinds joined Hello Games to create this passion project.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/no-mans-sky-dev-announces-new-game-the-last-campfire">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Colin Stevens</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:14:37Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dauntless Announced for PS4, Xbox One, Switch and Mobile</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/dauntless-announced-for-ps4-xbox-one-switch-and-mobile</link>
      <description>The online action-RPG Dauntless is officially coming to PlayStation 4, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch and mobile devices.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:06:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c08616be4b0c3a735a312e5</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The online action-RPG Dauntless is officially coming to PlayStation 4, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch and mobile devices.
</p><p>Announced at The Game Awards 2018, developer Phoenix Labs shared the news in a new trailer, revealing that the PS4 and Xbox one versions of the game will launch in April, and will become available on the Epic Games Store that same month. The Switch and mobile versions will come sometime later in 2019. The developer also revealed its “One Dauntless” initiative, providing cross-platform play, progression and account management across all of these devices, worldwide.
</p><p>Dauntless’ newest major content update, Frostfall, is being released today, bringing seasonal content like deep freeze descends on Ramsgate, and Slayers receiving a “chilling challenge” with the introduction of the new behemoth Valomyr. The Dauntless Hunt Pass was also launched today, providing players with new challenges, in-game activities, exclusive items and more for $10 USD.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/dauntless-announced-for-ps4-xbox-one-switch-and-mobile">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Colin Stevens</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:06:43Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter of Arcade Games Revealed</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/microsofts-winter-of-arcade-is-9-games-including-below-ashen-donut-county-and-more</link>
      <description>Microsoft's Winter of Arcade promotion highlights nine indie games with incentives for purchasing each one through December 21.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:00:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c084623e4b0775fa30ccda0</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today at The Game Awards, Microsoft detailed its Winter of Arcade promotion – a program that highlights nine indie games with incentives for purchasing each one from December 4 through December 21.
</p><p>You can find the games included in the promotion and their release dates below:
</p><p><h2><span style="color: #d51d29">Winter of Arcade Games and Dates</span></h2>
</p><p><ul>
</p><p>	<li>Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom – Dec. 4</li>
</p><p>	<li>Mutant Year Zero (Xbox Game Pass included) (<a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/04/mutant-year-zero-road-to-eden-review" target="_blank">IGN Review</a>) – Dec. 4</li>
</p><p>	<li>Subnautica 1.0 (<a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/01/26/subnautica-review" target="_blank">IGN Review</a>) – Dec. 4</li>
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/microsofts-winter-of-arcade-is-9-games-including-below-ashen-donut-county-and-more">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Brandin Tyrrel</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:00:41Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obsidian Announces New Sci-Fi RPG The Outer Worlds</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/obsidian-announces-new-sci-fi-rpg-the-outer-worlds</link>
      <description>Set in a far-off colony on the brink of corporate collapse, Obsidian's new single-player RPG is a dark, humorous science fiction shooter.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:00:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c098f38e4b0b6ea190c953e</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today during The Game Awards, developer Obsidian Entertainment and publisher Private Division have announced The Outer Worlds, a new single-player, sci-fi RPG for Xbox One, PS4, and PC coming in 2019.
</p><p>Set on a colony at the edge of the galaxy where corporations have taken over every aspect of life, your character awakens from hibernation in the midst of a conspiracy that threatens the survival of the colony on the brink of collapse.
</p><p>As a true single-player RPG, you can build your character into several different playstyles, choose and manage your companions, and drive the story through your decision making, branching dialog, and the actions you take.
</p><p>The Outer Worlds appears to be a bleak take on commercialism run amok with a strong undercurrent of dark humor throughout the setting and characters.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/obsidian-announces-new-sci-fi-rpg-the-outer-worlds">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Brandin Tyrrel</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:00:17Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioWare Teases New Dragon Age Game</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/new-dragon-age-teased-by-bioware</link>
      <description>BioWare's fantasy RPG series will be back in the coming years, but for now, details are scarce.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 03:00:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09b8d8e4b0775fa30ccf19</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During The Game Awards, BioWare teased the next installment of the Dragon Age franchise.
</p><p>Though details are scarce BioWare revealed a brief video for the upcoming RPG that ended with the hashtag #TheDreadWolfRises.
</p><p><p style="text-align: center"><strong>SPOILERS for Dragon Age: Inquisition below:</strong></p>
</p><p>The Dread Wolf is a reference to an elven deity in the Dragon Age lore, named Fen'Harel, who as it turns out is actually the player's companion Solas.
</p><p>In Dragon Age: Inquisition's Trespasser DLC, Solas is revealed to be the entity known as the Dread Wolf, before walking through a portal into obscurity. It seems the next game in the Dragon Age series will focus at least somewhat on where he's been and what he's doing.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/new-dragon-age-teased-by-bioware">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Brandin Tyrrel</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T03:00:11Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash Team Racing Remaster Announced</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/crash-team-racing-remaster-announced-release-date-revealed</link>
      <description>A Crash Team Racing remaster is real, and already has a release date.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:58:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c096dabe4b0775fa30cce94</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Activision has announced that a Crash Team Racing remaster is real, and already has a release date.
</p><p>Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled will be released on June 21, 2019 for PS4, Xbox One, and Nintendo Switch, Activision confirmed at The Game Awards following an orange dice-fueled tease earlier this week.
</p><p>Nitro-Fueled is developed by Spider-Man: Shattered Dimensions devs Beenox Interactive and brings back all the original content from the original PlayStation's CTR, built from the ground up with new visuals and audio. All characters, tracks, and arenas will return, with Adventure, Arcade Single and Cup Race, Time Trials, and Battle modes all returning. Nitro-Fueled will also feature online multiplayer for these modes.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/crash-team-racing-remaster-announced-release-date-revealed">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jonathon Dornbush</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T02:58:55Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthem's Story Trailer Reveals a New Villain</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/anthem-story-trailer-reveals-new-villain</link>
      <description>At the 2018 Game Awards, BioWare unveiled its first story-driven trailer for Anthem.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:54:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c099cbde4b0775fa30cced2</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the 2018 Game Awards show in Los Angeles, EA and BioWare unveiled the first story trailer for its upcoming online multiplayer action RPG, Anthem. While the trailer is short, there are important narrative details that shed light on the NPCs you'll interact with, and the motivations behind our heroes' adventures as they venture out into a hostile world that forces them to wear armored Javelin suits and fight big scary things.
</p><p>At a press briefing just before the Game Awards, IGN spoke to Anthem's game director, Jonathan Warner, along with lead producer Michael Gamble about what you can expect to find from a story perspective when the game launches on Feb. 22.
</p><p><h2><span style="color: #ff0000">The Anthem of Creation</span></h2>
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/anthem-story-trailer-reveals-new-villain">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <media:content height="405" type="image/jpeg" width="720" url="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2018/12/ANTHEM_VGA_Screens_SH002_FINAL_LOGO_16X9-720x405.jpg">
        <media:description type="html">id=</media:description>
      </media:content>
      <dc:creator>David Griffin</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T02:54:44Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bastion, Transition Game Studio Announces New Game</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/hades-announced-by-supergiant-games</link>
      <description>Supergiant Games' next project challenges you to escape hell.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:36:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09dcb7e4b0b6ea190c95c3</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hades is the next game by Supergiant Games, and it's now available in Early Access on the Epic Games Store.
</p><p>The rouge-like dungeon crawler was announced at The Game Awards and, as of right now, is only available on PC for $20 USD. The official Hades <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/store/en-US/product/hades/home">website</a> says to "expect regular updates with new features, events, characters, places, powers, and more."
</p><p>Hades is Supergiant Games' first Early Access project and its <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/store/en-US/product/hades/faq">FAQ</a> promises support for the game for at least "a year and a half from </p><p> initial launch." The FAQ also says that the Early Access launch build doesn't have an endpoint and can be played "indefinitely due to its structure and design." The end of the story will be saved for when development is finished.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/hades-announced-by-supergiant-games">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Miranda Sanchez</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T02:36:39Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubisoft Reveals Far Cry New Dawn</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/ubisoft-reveals-far-cry-new-dawn</link>
      <description>Ubisoft has revealed what happened to the world after Far Cry 5 ended with the upcoming entry, New Dawn.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:29:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c07f2fee4b0775fa30cccff</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At The Game Awards tonight, Ubisoft announced a standalone sequel to Far Cry 5 titled Far Cry New Dawn.
</p><p>Set 17 years after a global nuclear disaster, Far Cry New Dawn drops players into a beautiful yet transformed Hope County, Montana – the primary setting of Far Cry 5.
</p><p>The player will be cast in the role of a survivor facing an entirely new threat in the form of the Highwaymen, a band of scavengers, led by The Twins, Mickey and Lou – the main antagonists of New Dawn.
</p><p>Players will be tasked with mounting a resistance and strengthening the Survivors camp, who live in a base known as Prosperity. This is where players will be able craft ramshackle weapons and vehicles and recruit new Guns for Hire, which are said to include "new and familiar faces". But more intriguingly, this will also be where players access 'Expeditions', which for the first time in the series take players beyond the core map. These Expeditions are said to take place in "memorable locations across the US, from wetlands to canyons and more".
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/ubisoft-reveals-far-cry-new-dawn">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Daniel Krupa</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T02:29:31Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch The Game Awards 2018 Live Right Now</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/the-game-awards-2018-nominations-announced</link>
      <description>Find out when and where you'll be able to watch this year's big video game awards show.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:23:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5beafe84e4b0b6ea190c725b</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Update: </strong>The Game Awards 2018 is now live.
</p><p><strong>You can watch the show live in the player below (or <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QACMx7_AXlE" target="_blank">here on YouTube)</a>:</strong>
</p><p>The Game Awards 2018 takes place on December 6, and you'll be able to watch the event live, right here on IGN.
</p><p>In addition to recognizing the best games of the year, The Game Awards has historically featured several big reveals. All of the major announcements are being kept under wraps, but <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/11/30/5-predictions-for-the-2018-game-awards" target="_blank">we have a few ideas about what surprises</a> this year's show might have in store.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/the-game-awards-2018-nominations-announced">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jessie Wade</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T02:23:39Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3: The Black Order Announced For Switch</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/marvel-ultimate-alliance-3-the-black-order-announced-for-nintendo-switch</link>
      <description>Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3: The Black Order was just announced for a 2019 release, exclusively for Switch.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:14:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09d76de4b0c3a735a31461</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3: The Black Order was just announced for a 2019 release, exclusively for the Nintendo Switch, at the Game Awards.
</p><p>The third entry in the action RPG series was announced with a trailer, which showed off featured characters like the Hulk, Spider-Man, the Guardians of the Galaxy and Wolverine fighting against enemies like Green Goblin, the Sentinels and many more. It features a new top-down view and will be developed by Koei Tecmo Games and Team Ninja and published by Nintendo.
</p><p>Per a press release, Marvel Ultimate Alliance 3: The Black Order will bring together familiar heroes and villains across the Marvel Universe to battle for the Infinity Gauntlet. "This unprecedented team of characters must use their unique superpowers to defeat the mad cosmic tyrant Thanos and his ruthless warmasters, The Black Order."
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/marvel-ultimate-alliance-3-the-black-order-announced-for-nintendo-switch">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Lucy O'Brien</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T02:14:20Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stanley Parable: Ultra Deluxe Coming to Consoles, PC in 2019</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/the-stanley-parable-ultra-deluxe-coming-to-consoles-pc-in-2019</link>
      <description>The Stanley Parable: Ultra Deluxe comes to consoles and PC in 2019 with all-new content and endings.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 02:08:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09d617e4b0775fa30ccf55</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Stanley Parable is coming to consoles in 2019 as The Stanley Parable: Ultra Deluxe.
</p><p>This new version of The Stanley Parable will feature new content, new choices, and new endings. It'll also come bundled with the original game.
</p><p>The Stanley Parable: Ultra Deluxe will be released for both PC and consoles, though specific platforms were not announced.
</p><p>The Stanley Parable was originally released on PC in 2013. <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2013/10/18/the-stanley-parable-review" target="_blank">IGN's review</a> called it "witty, unusual and quietly discomfiting."
</p><p><em>Jordan is a freelance writer for IGN.</em></p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/the-stanley-parable-ultra-deluxe-coming-to-consoles-pc-in-2019">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Jordan Sirani</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T02:08:59Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device 6 Dev Announces Nintendo Switch Game Sayonara Wild Hearts</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/device-6-dev-announces-nintendo-switch-game-sayonara-wild-hearts</link>
      <description>At the Game Awards 2018, Device 6 developer Simogo and Annapurna Interactive announced Sayonara Wild Hearts for the Nintendo Switch.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:59:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09d366e4b0b6ea190c95b0</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the Game Awards 2018, Device 6 developer Simogo and Annapurna Interactive announced Sayonara Wild Hearts for the Nintendo Switch.
</p><p>Described as a "Pop Album Video Game," Sayonara Wild Hearts is a stylistic music-based game featuring characters based on tarot cards, with names such as Dancing Devils, Howling Moons, Stereo Lovers, Hermit64, Little Death, and The Fool.
</p><p>Sayonara Wild Hearts features everything from riding motorcycles and skateboards, wielding swords, fighting three-headed wolves and more.
</p><p>Featuring a custom-written vocal pop soundtrack that was designed to complement the gameplay, Sayonara Wild Hearts focuses on "synthesizing electric pop, dance, fashion, anime, arcade games and subcultures, and much more."
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/device-6-dev-announces-nintendo-switch-game-sayonara-wild-hearts">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Adam Bankhurst</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T01:59:11Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journey to the Savage Planet Announced at The Game Awards</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/journey-to-the-savage-planet-announced-at-the-game-awards</link>
      <description>Journey to the Savage Planet, the debut title from Typhoon Studios, has been announced at The Game Awards 2018 and will be coming to the Xbox One, PlayStation 4 and PC in 2019.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:48:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c059deae4b0b6ea190c9216</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Journey to the Savage Planet, the debut title from Typhoon Studios, has been announced at The Game Awards 2018 and will be coming to the Xbox One, PlayStation 4 and PC in 2019.
</p><p>An “upbeat first-person adventure game” set in a vibrant alien world, the player assumes the role of a Kindred Aerospace employee, which is the “4th Best Interstellar Exploration Company.” Players will explore an uncharted planet on the far corners of the universe: with no real plan and little equipment, players will have to explore, catalogue alien lifeforms and determine if the planet is fit for human habitation.
</p><p>Typhoon Studios is a Montreal-based team comprised of various industry veterans, including Alex Hutchinson (Far Cry 4, Assassin’s Creed 3), Yassine Riahi and Reid Schneider (Batman: Arkham Origins).
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/journey-to-the-savage-planet-announced-at-the-game-awards">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Colin Stevens</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T01:48:06Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds on PS4 Live with Sydnee Goodman</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/playerunknowns-battlegrounds-on-ps4-gameplay-with-sydnee-goodman-ign-plays-live</link>
      <description>PUBG Corporation's Dave Curd is guiding Sydnee through the world of PUBG on PS4 in the hopes of earning that chicken dinner.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 01:31:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09c313e4b0775fa30ccf35</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Break out those frying pans, because Sydnee Goodman and PUBG Corporation's Dave Curd are out for a chicken dinner.
</p><p>Come stop by to see the game in action on PlayStation 4 this Friday, December 7, starting at 10am PT/1pm ET.
</p><p><a href="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2018/12/SydneePlaysLive-PUBG_YT.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2065957" alt="SydneePlaysLive-PUBG_YT" src="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2018/12/SydneePlaysLive-PUBG_YT.jpg" width="1280" height="720" /></a>
</p><p>As always, you can watch right here on the front page of IGN.com, or you can find us on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/ign">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/ign">Twitch</a>, and <a href="https://mixer.com/IGN">Mixer</a>.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/playerunknowns-battlegrounds-on-ps4-gameplay-with-sydnee-goodman-ign-plays-live">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <media:content height="720" type="image/jpeg" width="1280" url="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2018/12/SydneePlaysLive-PUBG_YT.jpg"/>
      <dc:creator>Nick Limon</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-07T01:31:28Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counter-Strike: Global Offensive Is Now Free-To-Play, Battle Royale Mode Added</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/counter-strike-global-offensive-is-now-free-to-play-battle-royale-mode-added</link>
      <description>Counter-Strike: Global Offensive is officially free-to-play on PC and Mac, and a new, smaller scale battle royale mode has been added.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:57:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c09b6d3e4b0775fa30ccf13</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Counter-Strike: Global Offensive is officially free-to-play on PC and Mac, and a new, smaller scale battle royale mode has been added.
</p><p>Announced through <a href="http://counter-strike.net/dangerzone" target="_blank">counter-strike.net</a>, the mode is called Danger Zone, and is played by 16 players at a time (this can go up to 18 if players queue as a squad of two or three). This battle royale mode revolves around a tablet that characters can use, seeing a visual representation of where the Danger Zone is closing in as the match progresses.
</p><p>The tablet can also track the movements of other players and their drone deliveries, allowing you to strategically use this information to your advantage. The tablet can be upgraded to gain more detailed intel on the ever-changing Danger Zone.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/counter-strike-global-offensive-is-now-free-to-play-battle-royale-mode-added">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>Colin Stevens</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-06T23:57:36Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aww Yes, It's Time For Super Smash Brothers Ultimate!</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/aww-yes-its-time-for-super-smash-brothers-ultimate-nvc-ep-435</link>
      <description>This week's episode is devoted entirely to Monster Boy. JUST KIDDING. It's about Smash.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 23:00:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0986eae4b0c3a735a313cc</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WEEEEEEELLLLLLLLCOOOOOMME! Great news everyone, IT'S TIME FOR SMASH. That's right, all of your favorites in one game, just pummeling each other. We're dedicating the back half of the show to Super Smash Bros. Ultimate, but up front, we'll tell you about GRIS, Monster Boy and the Cursed Kingdom and a few others. This week's cast: <a href="https://twitter.com/ZachariusD">Zachary Ryan</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/PeerIGN">Peer Schneider</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/TomRMarks">Tom Marks</a>, and <a href="https://twitter.com/agentbizzle">Brian Altano</a>.
</p><p>Take a look at Tom's Review for Super Smash Bros. Ultimate here:
</p><p>And, just for funsies, here's EVERY final Smash:
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/aww-yes-its-time-for-super-smash-brothers-ultimate-nvc-ep-435">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <media:content height="64" type="image/png" width="268" url="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2015/05/Subscribe-to-this-show.png"/>
      <dc:creator>Zachary Ryan</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-06T23:00:36Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Not Too Late to Preorder Super Smash Bros. Ultimate</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/super-smash-bros-release-date-collectors-edition-preorder</link>
      <description>Smash Bros. comes out tomorrow. Don't miss a second of the action!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 21:44:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bfd6bbfe4b0b6ea190c8e11</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>If you buy something through this post, IGN may get a share of the sale. For more, read our <a href="https://www.ziffdavis.com/terms-of-use#endorsement">Terms of Use</a>.</em>
</p><p>The reviews are in. Super Smash Bros. Ultimate is amazing. In fact, we scored it as such in our <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/super-smash-bros-ultimate-review" target="_blank">Super Smash Bros. Ultimate review</a>. If you haven't preordered it yet, it's not too late. In fact, you can go ahead and get everything you possibly need to start Smashing right away with this helpful guide to everything you need.
</p><p>With a roster of 74 fighters, an unparalleled number of songs on the soundtrack, and something like 1,300 spirits, it's as much a love-letter to gaming as it is a competitive fighting game.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/super-smash-bros-release-date-collectors-edition-preorder">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <media:content height="350" type="image/jpeg" width="216" url="http://oyster.ignimgs.com/wordpress/stg.ign.com/2018/06/003Smash.jpg"/>
      <dc:creator>Seth G. Macy</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-06T21:44:56Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imperator: Rome Has Deadly Forests and Emergency Dictator Powers</title>
      <link>http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/imperator-rome-hands-on-tribal-migrations-deadly-forests-and-emergency-powers</link>
      <description>A trip back into history in Paradox's latest deep strategy game.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 20:40:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0866b1e4b0c3a735a312f4</guid>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Historically, the later period of the Western Roman Empire was heavily shaped by the migration of barbarian Germanic tribes into their former lands, paving the way for medieval states. Imperator: Rome, Paradox’s upcoming grand strategy game about the classical world, starts several centuries earlier than that in a time when Rome was just beginning its rise to power. But when I heard barbarian migrations had been implemented as a launch feature, I didn’t let the date on the calendar stop me from kicking the party off early.
</p><p>Imperator is based around population units called pops, a concept that may be familiar to players of other Paradox games like Stellaris and Victoria II. These are the people that live in all of the thousands of cities on the map. They can be encouraged to move, they can decline and die, or they can multiply as history marches on. Germanic barbarian tribes have the ability to uproot their pops and turn them into mobile armies, leaving their former homes uninhabited and allowing them to seek new ones.
</p><p><a href="http://www.ign.com/articles/2018/12/06/imperator-rome-hands-on-tribal-migrations-deadly-forests-and-emergency-powers">Continue reading&hellip;</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <dc:creator>T.J. Hafer</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2018-12-06T20:40:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
